onescrappymom.com 2014-12-23

# Privacy Policy | Think. Talk. Blog.

At ThinkTalkBlog.com, I recognize that privacy of your personal information is important.

The following is information about what types of personal information I receive and collect when you use and visit ThinkTalkBlog.com, and how we safeguard your information.

**Log File**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features.

**Third Party Advertisements**  
We also use third party advertisements on ThinkTalkBlog.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing Las Vegas real estate ads to someone in Las Vegas, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site, as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices. as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Email Address**  
We collect the e-mail addresses of visitors, including those who post messages to our site. We are not sharing any of those email addresses to any third party.

**External Links**  
By visiting the external links shown in Link page of this site, visitors are stipulated with the Privacy Policy and Terms of Services of respective web sites they visits.

**Giveaways**  
If you enter in one of my giveaways, please understand that the information you provide in that giveaway will be used by me to contact with you, and ultimately shared with the company that is sponsoring the giveaway. Please be familiar with the privacy policy of companies that offer sponsorships on ThinkTalkBlog.com, so that you better understand what they will do with your information once they receive it.

**Summing It Up**  
Cookies are common on most websites these days, and they contain information that is helpful to your overall browsing experience. This site, like many others, use them. But, I do nothing with the information I receive about the pages you visit, the email address you leave in a comment, etc. Your information is your own, and I would never knowingly make a decision about this website that would compromise your privacy.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact me](http://thinktalkblog.com/contact/ "Contact Bobbie").
